Festus Ebin

Software Engineer

77 Idimu Road, Ejigbo, Lagos +234 806 034 0774 festusebin@gmail.com linktr.ee/festusebin

About

Creates better user experiences via visual storytelling that solves real-life problems.

Forward-thinking approach with Agile methodologies and engineering principles in creating functional and responsive websites and apps.

Skills (soft)

- Critical & analytical thinking
- Creative problem-solving
- Team building/Leadership
- Continuous improvement
- Mentoring relationships
- Initiative and enterprise

Connect with me







Work Experience

Jan 2019 - March 2020

Frontend Developer at Algeebra Technologies

Liaises with project beneficiaries and stakeholders during project preparation and development of the software application. Facilitates the training of support staff and enumerators for the conduct of qualitative and quantitative data for client projects. Acts as Customer relations officer, especially handling customer technical inquiries while also ensuring prompt resolution of complaint.

July 2016 - Dec 2016

Software Developer (Intern) at Raoatech IT Limited

Regularly prepared student records and transactional report; ensuring that the key performance indicators (KPIs) are monitored. Carried out software development lifecycle (SDLC) documentation, analysis data and online behaviour pertaining to clients. Planned and coordinated departmental group project report for the company.

Education

2016 - 2017

Full Stack Web Development, freeCodeCamp

November 2012 - December 2017

B.Sc. (Systems Engineering), University of Lagos, Akoka, Lagos

Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

UX/UI Design & Frontend Developemnt, Univelcity, Lagos

Dec 2019 - April 2020

Software Engineering, Stutern SGA, Lagos

March 2020 - May 2020

Software Engineering, StartNG, HNG

Skills (technical)

VS Code

Git & GitHub

Figma

User Experience Design (UX)

User Interface Design (UI)

HTML/CSS/JS/React JS

Node JS/Express/MongoDB

Interests







Sci-fi







Travel

Surfing

Tennis

Gaming

Football